https://www.zafire.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy and the security of your personal information is our highest priority.
In compliance with GDPR we have updated our privacy policy:
Be informed on how we are using your data
Access the data we have on you
Rectification on any inaccurate information
Erasure of all data we have on you
For more details please read below, if you would like to preform any of the above actions please email GDPR@zafire.com, if you would like to make a complaint, please see the ICO complaint page
Be Informed
How we collect Information
There are several methods that we may collect your information from. If you visit our website and fill in one of our online forms your information is submitted to us, similarly if you contact us via email with an enquiry we will also receive your information. When you contact us in person of via phone we may ask for your information.
When you submit your information to us we will enter it into our CRM system.
What information we collect
We may collect any of the below:
Name
Address
Email
Phone
Place of work
Position
What product you may be interested in
What we do with it
When we enter your information into our CRM system we may contact you with product information, product enquiries and requests or market research. We may contact you via email or phone.
If you decided you would not like to be contacted by us please email GDPR@zafire.com  you will not receive any further information from us. You can also or unsubscribe from our mailing list at any time by clicking “Unsubscribe” at the top of our emails.
We do not share this information with third parties
Access
You can receive a copy of your data from us at any time, by emailing GDPR@zafire.com  this will be completed within a month in a clear and accessible manner.
Rectification
If you find that our information is not accurate or would like to update it you may do this at any time by emailing GDPR@zafire.com
Erasure
You have the right to request that your information is deleted at any time, you also have the right to request your information from us is a clear an concise manner.
As of May 2018 we will hold your data for 5 years, after this time we will remove your information from our system.
—————————————————————–
Privacy Policy for Zafire Group Limited Mobile Applications:
Zafire Group Mobile Applications collects some Personal Data from their Users.
POLICY OVERVIEW
Personal Data collected for the following purposes and using the following services:
Device permissions for Personal Data access
Personal Data: Camera permission, Microphone permission, Phone permission and Precise location permission (continuous)
FULL POLICY
Data Controller and Owner
Types of Data collected
Among the types of Personal Data that this Application collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: Camera permission, Precise location permission (continuous), Microphone permission and Phone permission.
Other Personal Data collected may be described in other sections of this privacy policy or by dedicated explanation text contextually with the Data collection.
The Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or collected automatically when using this Application.
Any use of Cookies – or of other tracking tools – by this Application or by the owners of third party services used by this Application, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify Users and remember their preferences, for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User.
Failure to provide certain Personal Data may make it impossible for this Application to provide its services.
Users are responsible for any Personal Data of third parties obtained, published or shared through this Application and confirm that they have the third party’s consent to provide the Data to the Owner.
Mode and place of processing the Data
Methods of processing
The Data Controller processes the Data of Users in a proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Data.
The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Data Controller, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of the site (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Data Controller at any time.
Place
The Data is processed at the Data Controller’s operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved with the processing are located. For further information, please contact the Data Controller.
Retention time
The Data is kept for the time necessary to provide the service requested by the User, or stated by the purposes outlined in this document, and the User can always request that the Data Controller suspend or remove the data.
The use of the collected Data
The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Owner to provide its services, as well as for the following purposes: Device permissions for Personal Data access.
The Personal Data used for each purpose is outlined in the specific sections of this document.
Device permissions for Personal Data access
Depending on the User’s specific device, this Application may request certain permissions that allow it to access the User’s device Data as described below.
By default, these permissions must be granted by the User before the respective information can be accessed. Once the permission has been given, it can be revoked by the User at any time. In order to revoke these permissions, Users may refer to the device settings or contact the Owner for support at the contact details provided in the present document.
The exact procedure for controlling app permissions may be dependent on the User’s device and software.
Please note that the revoking of such permissions might impact the proper functioning of this Application.
If User grants any of the permissions listed below, the respective Personal Data may be processed (i.e accessed to, modified or removed) by this Application.
Camera permission
Used for accessing the camera or capturing images and video from the device.
Microphone permission
Used for accessing and recording microphone audio from the User’s device.
Phone permission
Used for accessing a host of typical features associated with telephony. This enables, for instance, read-only access to the “phone state”, which means it enables access to the phone number of the device, current mobile network information, or the status of any ongoing calls.
Precise location permission (continuous)
Used for accessing the User’s precise device location. This Application may collect, use, and share User Location Data in order to provide location-based services.
Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data
Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:
Device permissions for Personal Data access
This Application requests certain permissions from Users that allow it to access the User’s device Data as described below.
Device permissions for Personal Data access (This Application)
This Application requests certain permissions from Users that allow it to access the User’s device Data as summarized here and described within this document.
Personal Data collected: Camera permission, Microphone permission, Phone permission and Precise location permission (continuous).
Additional information about Data collection and processing
Legal action
The User’s Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Data Controller, in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Application or the related services.
The User declares to be aware that the Data Controller may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities.
Additional information about User’s Personal Data
In addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, this Application may provide the User with additional and contextual information concerning particular services or the collection and processing of Personal Data upon request.
System logs and maintenance
For operation and maintenance purposes, this Application and any third party services may collect files that record interaction with this Application (System logs) or use for this purpose other Personal Data (such as IP Address).
Information not contained in this policy
More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Data Controller at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document.
The rights of Users
Users have the right, at any time, to know whether their Personal Data has been stored and can consult the Data Controller to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Data Controller at the contact information set out above.
This Application does not support “Do Not Track” requests.
To determine whether any of the third party services it uses honour the “Do Not Track” requests, please read their privacy policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
The Data Controller reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. If a User objects to any of the changes to the Policy, the User must cease using this Application and can request that the Data Controller remove the Personal Data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current privacy policy applies to all Personal Data the Data Controller has about Users.
Information about this privacy policy
The Data Controller is responsible for this privacy policy.
Definitions and legal references
Personal Data (or Data)
Any information regarding a natural person, a legal person, an institution or an association, which is, or can be, identified, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number.
Usage Data
Information collected automatically from this Application (or third party services employed in this Application), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use this Application, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server’s answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User’s IT environment.
User
The individual using this Application, which must coincide with or be authorized by the Data Subject, to whom the Personal Data refers.
Data Subject
The legal or natural person to whom the Personal Data refers.
Data Processor (or Data Supervisor)
The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization authorized by the Data Controller to process the Personal Data in compliance with this privacy policy.
Data Controller (or Owner)
The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization with the right, also jointly with another Data Controller, to make decisions regarding the purposes, and the methods of processing of Personal Data and the means used, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Application. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of this Application.
This Application
The hardware or software tool by which the Personal Data of the User is collected.
Legal information
Notice to European Users: this privacy statement has been prepared in fulfillment of the obligations under Art. 10 of EC Directive n. 95/46/EC, and under the provisions of Directive 2002/58/EC, as revised by Directive 2009/136/EC, on the subject of Cookies.
This privacy policy relates solely to the Zafire Group Limited Mobile Applications.
If you would like to discuss privacy issues with us please email info@zafire.com  or call us on +44 (0) 1295 701 810.
Comments are closed.
Privacy Policy
Back
